[
    {
        "id": 0,
        "question": "Cât face 1 + 1?",
        "answers": ["1", "2", "3", "4"],
        "correct": 1
    },
    {
        "id": 1,
        "question": "Cât face 2 + 2?",
        "answers": ["1", "2", "4", "3"],
        "correct": 2
    },
    {
        "id": 2,
        "question": "Care este rezultatul calculului 41 + 12?",
        "answers": ["53", "50", "63", "49"],
        "correct": 0
    },
    {
        "id": 3,
        "question": "Care este rezultatul calculului 59 + 38?",
        "answers": ["89", "93", "69", "97"],
        "correct": 3
    },
    {
        "id": 4,
        "question": "Cât face 104 + 59?",
        "answers": ["169", "170", "163", "161"],
        "correct": 2
    },
    {
        "id": 5,
        "question": "Cât face 174 + 16?",
        "answers": ["181", "187", "190", "193"],
        "correct": 2
    },
    {
        "id": 6,
        "question": "Cât face 147 + 299?",
        "answers": ["446", "441", "439", "450"],
        "correct": 0
    },
    {
        "id": 7,
        "question": "Cât face 239 + 245?",
        "answers": ["481", "484", "485", "487"],
        "correct": 1
    },
    {
        "id": 8,
        "question": "Cât face 519 + 231?",
        "answers": ["755", "748", "750", "751"],
        "correct": 2
    },
    {
        "id": 9,
        "question": "Cât face 1024 + 571?",
        "answers": ["1780", "1576", "1495", "1595"],
        "correct": 3
    }
]
